[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Constantine, while transporting himself to Hell, Constantine chooses using a cat for what what reason?", "correct_answer": "Cats are already half in and half out.", "incorrect_answers": ["Cats are Gods sacred animal and help protect him while in Hell.", "Cats are the direct route to hell, created originally for this purpose.", "Cats independent personalities are useful in Hell."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Rocky Balboa, what anniversary does Rocky commemorate every year by making pilgrimages to his favorite places?", "correct_answer": "Adrians death", "incorrect_answers": ["His sons birthday", "His wedding anniversary", "His first win against Apollo (in Rocky 2)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following owns the .fm domain name that is popular among radio stations?", "correct_answer": "Federated States of Micronesia", "incorrect_answers": ["International Broadcasters Union", "France", "Mexico"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first movie in which Butterfly McQueen appeared?", "correct_answer": "The Women", "incorrect_answers": ["Duel in the Sun", "Serenade in Black and  Blue", "Gone With the Wind"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not a name of a Calvin Klein fragrance?", "correct_answer": "Dolce Vita", "incorrect_answers": ["Euphoria", "Obsession", "cK be"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This comedienne/actress/writer was an up and coming director until she made the great flop Ishtar.", "correct_answer": "Elaine May", "incorrect_answers": ["Lee Grant", "Nora Ephron", "Sarah Jacobson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Can you name the 2004 television series the following quote is from: Me and 4,399 of my closest friends popped out of a ball of light right about here.", "correct_answer": "The 4400", "incorrect_answers": ["Taken", "Threshold", "V"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What plant symbolized the love between Andie and Benjamin in the 2003 romantic comedy How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days?", "correct_answer": "Fern", "incorrect_answers": ["Geranium", "Thornapple", "Rose"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is often put on the glass rim when serving a Margarita cocktail?", "correct_answer": "Salt", "incorrect_answers": ["Avocado slice", "Sugar", "An olive"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This person developed the first system to produce donatable blood plasma and was the first director of a Red Cross Blood Bank in the USA.", "correct_answer": "Charles Richard Drew", "incorrect_answers": ["William Osler", "Felix Bernstein", "Franklin McLean."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the role of Jimmy B-Rabbit in the 2002 movie 8 Mile, directed by Curtis Hanson?", "correct_answer": "Eminem", "incorrect_answers": ["Michael Shannon", "Kim Basinger", "Evan Jones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Sun is located at the center of our galaxy.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]